<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Zorbiks&#39; Blog</title>
    <link>https://zorbiks.vercel.app/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Zorbiks&#39; Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 15:07:00 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://zorbiks.vercel.app/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>F@#$ You Inwi</title>
      <link>https://zorbiks.vercel.app/blog/f-you-inwi/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 15:07:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zorbiks.vercel.app/blog/f-you-inwi/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I was happy that I could switch from a 12 Mbps ADSL connection to a 20 Mbps fiber optics. It was refreshing, although the speed wasn’t particularly impressive. still, for the same price I would definitely make the switch. At the time, Inwi was the only provider offering fiber optics in my area, so I switched like any sane person did. After a few months of use, problems began to appear. People told me that Inwi is a good company, but I didn’t realize I was simply talking to folks who use fiber optics for entertainment only. They aren’t tech‑savvy; all they know is that the internet is Google, cloud storage is in the air, and ChatGPT is a miracle.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Three Years at University Wasted?</title>
      <link>https://zorbiks.vercel.app/blog/three-years-at-university-wasted/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 23:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zorbiks.vercel.app/blog/three-years-at-university-wasted/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Before making any bad assumptions, let me clarify that I&amp;rsquo;m not dismissing the importance of attending college. It&amp;rsquo;s still a valuable investment in one&amp;rsquo;s education and can provide a competitive edge in the job market. However, I&amp;rsquo;d like to share my personal experience as a recent graduate.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Is university a waste of time? The answer depends on various factors. In my case, attending a public university was an okay experience, which I&amp;rsquo;d rate as 5 out of 10 for several reasons.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
